<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Marriott_Mina_house_title">Marriott Mina House Hotel</string>
    <string name="marriott_mina_house_description">Overlooking the Great Pyramids of Giza, Marriott Mena House,
        Cairo is surrounded by 40 acres of green gardens and has a spa, fitness centre and a pool.
        The rooms are decorated with handcrafted furniture.
        All accommodations at Marriott Mena House, Cairo have air conditioning and include luxurious fabrics,
        a seating area and LCD TV. Each room and suite has a spacious private bathroom with a bathrobe and slippers.
        Breakfast is available in the dining room facing the garden.
        Dining choices range from Italian specialties at Alfredo Restaurant,
        while Daily Buffet Breakfast and unforgettable vistas with its cocktails served at 139 Pavilion.
        Recreational Facilities include a heated swimming pool tucked away in the landscape gardens.
        The Giza Pyramids are less than half a kilometer from the Marriott Mena House.
        The concierge can arrange horse and camel rides to the pyramids. Cairo Airport is 30.6 km away.
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.4 for a two-person trip.

</string>
    <string name="fairmont_nile_City_title">Fairmont Nile City Hotel</string>
    <string name="fairmont_nile_City_description">Located in the Nile City Towers by the River Nile,
        this 5-star hotel features a rooftop pool deck with spectacular views across Cairo to the Pyramids. It offers 7 food and beverage venues.
        All of the Fairmont Nile City rooms are soundproof and decorated with elegant Art Deco furnishings.
        They come equipped with a work desk and interactive IPTV. The bathrooms have rain showers with sliding shutters.
        Some rooms offer a panoramic Nile view or city view.
        Fairmont Nile City provides modern equipment at its spacious fitness centre.
        There is also a well equipped business centre on site.
        Guests can enjoy gourmet dining at the Asian Fusion Saigon Restaurant and Lounge as well as Italian favorites at L’Uliveto.
        Guests can also enjoy Al fresco dining on the panoramic rooftop terrace. Bab El Nil offers night-time entertainment and Middle Eastern cuisine.
        Fairmont Nile City is located just 23.5 km from Cairo Int’l Airport and Cairo Museum is within 10 minutes drive away. Nile Towers Mall is footsteps away from the hotel.
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 8.6 for a two-person trip
</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_San_Stefano_title">Four Seasons San Stefano Hotel</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_San_Stefano_description">Set in an architectural landmark,
        Hotel San Stefano features a fashionable resort setting with a private sandy beach and overlooking the Mediterranean Sea.
        It boasts a full-service spa, outdoor pool and restaurants with terraces.
        Guests can enjoy free WiFi throughout the property and in the guest rooms.
        All rooms at the Four Seasons Hotel Alexandria At San Stefano have a balcony,
        some of them including Mediterranean Sea views.
        A minibar,TV and air conditioning are all standard facilities.
        The hotel has a 2 story Spa and fitness centre that offers 14 treatment rooms, sauna, steam room, whirlpool and a squash court.
        For leisure, the hotel provides a number of recreation activities year round based on seasonality: an outdoor infinity pool,
        an indoor heated pool, a private beach, Kids For all Seasons program and sightseeing.
        The hotel offers nine distinctive restaurants and lounges serving a diverse selection of local seafood and international specialties.
        Options range from Lebanese and Italian fine-dining to contemporary Mediterranean favourites – café snacks,
        cocktails and gelati. A Shisha corner is also available.
        The Alexandria Four Seasons Hotel is 60 km from Alexandria Borg El Arab Airport. A hotel limousine is available upon request.
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.3 for a two-person trip.</string>
    <string name="mövenpick_resort_Aswan_title">Mövenpick Resort Aswan Hotel</string>
    <string name="mövenpick_resort_Aswan_description">Set in an architectural landmark,
        Hotel San Stefano features a fashionable resort setting with a private sandy beach and overlooking the Mediterranean Sea.
        It boasts a full-service spa, outdoor pool and restaurants with terraces.
        Guests can enjoy free WiFi throughout the property and in the guest rooms.
        All rooms at the Four Seasons Hotel Alexandria At San Stefano have a balcony,
        some of them including Mediterranean Sea views.
        A minibar,TV and air conditioning are all standard facilities.
        The hotel has a 2 story Spa and fitness centre that offers 14 treatment rooms, sauna, steam room, whirlpool and a squash court.
        For leisure, the hotel provides a number of recreation activities year round based on seasonality: an outdoor infinity pool,
        an indoor heated pool, a private beach, Kids For all Seasons program and sightseeing.
        The hotel offers nine distinctive restaurants and lounges serving a diverse selection of local seafood and international specialties.
        Options range from Lebanese and Italian fine-dining to contemporary Mediterranean favourites – café snacks,
        cocktails and gelati. A Shisha corner is also available.
        The Alexandria Four Seasons Hotel is 60 km from Alexandria Borg El Arab Airport. A hotel limousine is available upon request.
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.3 for a two-person trip.</string>
    <string name="sofitel_winter_palace_Luxor_title">Sofitel Winter Palace Luxor Hotel</string>
    <string name="sofitel_winter_palace_Luxor_description">A stunning example of Victorian architecture,
        this prestigious hotel is a short walk from Luxor Temple and features high-standard facilities.
        Sofitel Winter Palace Luxor has a history of hosting royalty and celebrities throughout the years.
        The interior features grand staircases,
        high ceilings and lounge areas that are appointed with antique furniture and beautiful flower arrangements.
        As can be expected, Winter Palace\'s restaurants have a historical reputation to keep up to.
        Relax and socialize as you enjoy French cuisine with the latest fusion dishes from around the world.
        The pool scene is stunning and has the vibe of a private oasis with surrounding palm trees.
        A variety of convenient services are also offered at Winter Palace to deliver a memorable and stress-free holiday.
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.7 for a two-person trip.
</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_resort_sharm_El_Sheikh_title">Four Seasons Resort Sharm El Sheikh Hotel</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_resort_sharm_El_Sheikh_description">Four Seasons Resort is a hillside Red Sea diving resort set in Sharm El Sheikh.
        It boasts 4 pools, 5 restaurants, 3 lounges and a spa. Guests can also benefit from the snorkeling and diving activities available on site.
        All accommodation at Four Seasons feature a balcony or terrace with views of the Red Sea, the garden and the resort.
        Each room offers a seating area with a flat-screen TV and a minibar.
        The villa includes a private pool with a sun-lounger terrace.
        Four Seasons offers an eclectic fine dining experience ranging from Mediterranean to Italian Cuisine.
        Guests can savour European specialties at Al Waha Pool Bar that overlooks the pool.
        Drinks are enjoyed at the various lounges with spectacular views.
        The Four Seasons\'s spa offers a range of relaxation options, including full-body massages and facials.
        There is also a modern gym equipped with state-of-the-art cardiovascular equipment.
        For beauty purposes, a salon is also available.
        Four Seasons Resort Sharm El Sheikh is a 25-minute drive from Naama Bay. Old Sharm with its traditional markets,
        is 40 minutes by car. Sharm Al Sheikh Airport is 15 minutes by car.
        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.4 for a two-person trip</string>

</resources>