<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="mall_of_egypt_title">Mall of Egypt</string>
    <string name="mall_of_egypt_description">Details
        IMAGINE the best of local and international retailers, restaurants &amp; cafes,
        extraordinary entertainment experiences &amp; countless unforgettable Moments Together.
        Brought to you by Majid Al Futtaim</string>
    <string name="mall_of_Arabia_Cairo_title">Mall of Arabia Cairot</string>
    <string name="mall_of_Arabia_Cairo_description">Details
        Mall of Arabia is one of the top destinations in the country with more than 400 stores and attractions
        Additional Information
        Mall of Arabia welcomes more than 15 million visitors a year from across the country and
        around the world to enjoy over 400 retail and specialty stores.
        Experience unique dining and entertainment at over 30 restaurants.</string>
    <string name="khan_el_khalili_title">Khan el-Khalili</string>
    <string name="khan_el_khalili_description">Details
        ‎is a famous bazaar and souq (or souk) in the historic center of Cairo, Egypt.
        Established as a center of trade in the Mamluk era and named for one of its several historic caravanserais,
        the bazaar district has since become one of Cairo\'s main attractions for tourists and Egyptians alike.
        It is also home to many Egyptian artisans and workshops involved in the production of traditional crafts and souvenirs.</string>
    <string name="sOHO_Square_title">SOHO Square </string>
    <string name="sOHO_Square_description">Details
        SOHO Square™ Sharm El Sheikh brings a complete family, friends and couples entertainment centre to White Knight Bay,
        Sharm El Sheikh, with a range of entertainment including restaurants, cafés,
        bars and a club catering for tastes both young and old.
        Indulge in some fabulous high class shopping before sampling the exquisite international cuisine
        from one of our four themed à la carte restaurants.
        In the British house you can enjoy a pint at the authentic Queen Vic pub,
        before moving upstairs to the sushi and Teppanyaki bar or the fabulous steakhouse.
        Sharm El Sheikh has unleashed its best kept secret, nestled between the Savoy,
        Royal Savoy and the Sierra Hotels - SOHO Square™ Sharm El Sheikh.
        Created to appeal to a cross-genre of customers, renowned for providing the best selection of restaurants &amp; bars.
        Designed for experience with the ability to cater for all age groups,
        SOHO Square™ Sharm El Sheikh is a vibrant venue which has become the beacon of excellence within the town and the community.
        The Food &amp; Beverage outlets will definitely take centre stage on this multi-scene exclusive destination,
        serving the need for a true gourmet experience in Sharm El Sheikh.
        It has the ability to build bridges between nationalities through the language of exquisite restaurant food &amp; service,
        refined wines and vibrant entertainment.</string>

</resources>